bwfworldsuperseries.com 2019-03-21

# Terms & Conditions | BWF Fansite

**Terms and Conditions**

By using this website you are deemed to have read and agreed to the following terms and conditions.

The following terminology applies to these Terms and Conditions, Website Privacy Statement and Disclaimer Notice and any or all Agreements:

o   “Client”, “You” and “Your” refers to you, the person accessing this website and accepting the Badminton World Federation’s (“BWF”) terms and conditions.

o   “The BWF”, “Ourselves”, “We” and “Us”, refers to the Badminton World Federation (“BWF”).

o   “Party”, “Parties”, or “Us”, refers to both the Client and ourselves, or either the Client or ourselves.

o   All terms refer to the offer and acceptance necessary to undertake the process of our assistance to the Client in the most appropriate manner, for the express purpose of meeting the Client’s needs in respect of provision of the BWF’s stated services/products, in accordance with and subject to, prevailing Malaysian Law.

o   Any use of the above terminology or other words in the singular, plural, capitalisation and/or he/she or they, are taken as interchangeable and therefore as referring to same.

**Privacy Statement**

We are committed to protecting your privacy. You can visit the BWF Websites without disclosing any information about yourself. However, to participate in some of the BWF activities and opportunities presented on the website, you must register online and provide information on yourself so that the Services can be provided effectively and efficiently to you.

Activities include, but not limited to surveys, registration for courses, registering to receive information in the form of newsletters, e-news articles and notification of activities, products from the BWF, contests, forums, games, downloading content, receiving specific information from the BWF such as email and mobile alerts, news, results, tickets and partners offers, collectively known as the “Services”.

Authorized employees within the BWF on a need to know basis, only use any information collected from individual customers or the purpose for which it has been collected. We constantly review our systems and data to ensure the best possible Services to our Clients. BWF respects and follows all the relevant Laws of Malaysia when collecting, storing and using personal information gathered through the website with the express purpose of proving the Services for which the personal data was provided. **  
**

**Confidentiality**

Clients records are regarded as confidential and therefore these will not be divulged to any third party, other than to agencies contracted by BWF to affect the Services for which you have registered your personal details and if legally required to do so to the appropriate authorities.

Clients have the right to request sight of, and copies of any and all Client Records we keep, on the proviso that we are given reasonable notice of such a request. Clients are requested to retain copies of any literature issued in relation to the provision of our Services. Where appropriate, we shall issue Client’s with appropriate written information, handouts or copies of records as part of an agreed contract, for the benefit of both parties.

** ** We will not sell, share, or rent your personal information to any third party or use your e-mail address for unsolicited mail. Any emails sent by the BWF will only be in connection with the provision of agreed services and products.

#### **Disclaimer**

**Exclusions and Limitations**

The information on BWF websites is provided on an “as is” basis. To the fullest extent permitted by law, the BWF:

o    excludes all representations and warranties relating to this website and its contents or which is or may be provided by any affiliates or any other third party, including in relation to any inaccuracies or omissions in this website and/or the BWF’s literature; and

o     excludes all liability for damages arising out of or in connection with your use of this website. This includes, without limitation, direct loss, loss of business or profits (whether or not the loss of such profits was foreseeable, arose in the normal course of things or you have advised BWF of the possibility of such potential loss), damage caused to your computer, computer software, systems and programs and the data thereon or any other direct or indirect, consequential and incidental damages.

The above exclusions and limitations apply only to the extent permitted by law. None of your statutory rights as a consumer are affected.

**Termination of Agreements and Refunds Policy**

Both the Client and ourselves have the right to terminate any Services Agreement for any reason, including the ending of services that are already underway.

**Availability**

The BWF does not warrant that the service from this site will be uninterrupted, timely or error free, although it is provided to the best ability. By using this service you thereby indemnify the BWF, its employees, agents and affiliates against any loss or damage, in whatever manner, howsoever caused.

**Log Files  
**

We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. Additionally, for systems administration, detecting usage patterns and troubleshooting purposes, our web servers automatically log standard access information including browser type, access times/open mail, URL requested, and referral URL. This information is not shared with third parties and is used only within this Company on a need-to-know basis. Any individually identifiable information related to this data will never be used in any way different to that stated above without your explicit permission.

**Cookies**

Like most interactive web sites this Company’s website uses cookies to enable us to retrieve user details for each visit. Cookies are used in some areas of our site to enable the functionality of this area and ease of use for those people visiting. Some of our affiliate partners may also use cookies.

**Links to this Website**

You may not create a link to any page of this website without our prior written consent. If you do create a link to a page of this website you do so at your own risk and the exclusions and limitations set out above will apply to your use of this website by linking to it.

**Links from this Website**

We do not monitor or review the content of other party’s websites which are linked to or from this website.

Opinions expressed or material appearing on such websites are not necessarily shared or endorsed by us and should not be regarded as the publisher of such opinions or material.

Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices, or content, of these sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site & to read the privacy statements of these sites. You should evaluate the security and trustworthiness of any other site connected to this site or accessed through this site yourself, before disclosing any personal information to them.

BWF will not accept any responsibility for any loss or damage in whatever manner, howsoever caused, resulting from your disclosure to third parties of personal information.

**Intellectual Property**

The content of this website, including BWF’s logo, name, and other marks, as well as any multimedia content, is the property of BWF or used under license by BWF. No part of this website may be copied, republished, stored, or otherwise republished or transmitted, in any form or by any means whatsoever, without the prior written permission of BWF (which may be provided, for example, in a notice on the website). Unless otherwise provided, BWF is the owner or licensee of all copyright and other intellectual property rights on this website, and in the material published on it. All such rights are reserved.

For further information, or to request permission to use any of the content on BWF’s website, please contact: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**Communication  
**

We have several different e-mail addresses for different queries. These and other contact information, can be found on our [Office page](http://bwfcorporate.com/about/office/ "Contact Us") link on our Corporate website or via BWF literature or via the BWF’s stated telephone, facsimile or mobile telephone numbers.

This company is registered in Malaysia.

**Force Majeure  
**

Neither party shall be liable to the other for any failure to perform any obligation under any Agreement which is due to an event beyond the control of such party including but not limited to any Act of God, terrorism, war, political insurgence, insurrection, riot, civil unrest, act of civil or military authority, uprising, earthquake, flood or any other natural or man made eventuality outside of our control, which causes the termination of an agreement or contract entered into, nor which could have been reasonably foreseen.

Any Party affected by such event shall forthwith inform the other Party of the same and shall use all reasonable endeavours to comply with the terms and conditions of any Agreement contained herein.

**Waiver**

Failure of either Party to insist upon strict performance of any provision of this or any Agreement or the failure of either Party to exercise any right or remedy to which it, he or they are entitled hereunder shall not constitute a waiver thereof and shall not cause a diminution of the obligations under this or any Agreement. No waiver of any of the provisions of this or any Agreement shall be effective unless it is expressly stated to be such and signed by both Parties.

### **General**

The Laws of Malaysia govern these terms and conditions.

By accessing this website and using our services and buying our products when available, you consent to these terms and conditions and to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Malaysian courts in all disputes arising out of such access.

If any of these terms are deemed invalid or unenforceable for any reason (including, but not limited to the exclusions and limitations set out above), then the invalid or unenforceable provision will be severed from these terms and the remaining terms will continue to apply.

Failure of the BWF to enforce any of the provisions set out in these Terms and Conditions and any Agreement, or failure to exercise any option to terminate, shall not be construed as waiver of such provisions and shall not affect the validity of these Terms and Conditions or of any Agreement or any part thereof, or the right thereafter to enforce each and every provision. These Terms and Conditions shall not be amended, modified, varied or supplemented except in writing and signed by duly authorised representatives of the Company.

**Notification of Changes**

The BWF reserves the right to change these conditions from time to time as it sees fit and your continued use of the site will signify your acceptance of any adjustment to these terms. If there are any changes to our privacy policy, we will announce that these changes have been made on our home page and on other key pages on our site. If there are any changes in how we use our site customers’ Personally Identifiable Information, notification by e-mail or postal mail will be made to those affected by this change. Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on our web site 30 days prior to these changes taking place. You are therefore advised to re-read this statement on a regular basis

**These terms and conditions form part of the Agreement between the Client and ourselves. Your accessing of this website and/or undertaking of a booking or Agreement indicates your understanding, agreement to and acceptance, of the Disclaimer Notice and the full Terms and Conditions contained herein. Your statutory Consumer Rights are unaffected.**

© Badminton World Federation 2014 – All Rights Reserved
